<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gardenizer</string>
    <string name="my_garden">My Garden</string>
    <string name="picture_wildflowers">picture of wildflowers</string>

    <string name="januar_text"><b>It\'s winter!</b> \nDon\'t forget to remove snow from roofs, plants and paths
        \ndo the winter cut on your fruit trees\nstart sowing tomatos, bell pepper and annual summerflowers on your window sill
        \nif you have a nesting box outside: check if it is clean and has enough birdseed
        \nyour compost could do with a good stir and sieving </string>

    <string name="february_text"><b>It is still cooooold...</b> \n think about the poor little starving birds and put birdseeds into the nesting boxes
        \nnow it is time for prepare the soil for the closer getting garden season
        \nif the soil is not deeply frozen you can prepare the first plant holes for March and April
        \nif you have italian grape-vine now is the time to trim it!</string>

    <string name="march_text"><b>Spring is coming! Or is it really?</b> \nThe ground and soil is slowly starting to warm up, you can start preparing the first sowing like cauliflower, parsley and parsnips
        \nLet early potatoes bud on your window sill
        \nprepare the soil in your potatoe bed
        \nfertilise your fruit trees and
        \nput up some insect hotels for some buzzing and action in spring and summer!</string>

    <string name="april_text"><b>Sun! Rain! Hail! Frost! </b>
        \nit\'s time to sow your potatoes into the prepared soil!
        \nhave a look at your herbs: now is the time to cut, plant or sow your thyme, salvia, rosemary, oregano and mint
        \nif you plan on having (more) fruit trees or bushes: now is the time them</string>
    <string name="may_text"><b>Last but not least...</b>\nIt\'s May after all! Not long and you can buy and maybe pick your first strawberries!
        \nOne vegetable which is now ready to be picked and prepared is rhubarb, perfect for compot, cake or chutney.
        \nput the potatoes into the wonderfully prepared bed, it is very important to pile the soil very well, don\'t let the potatoes get ruined by the sun
        \nkeep your plants safe from snails, which are now coming out, hungry for freshly growing vegetables...</string>

    <string name="june_text"><b>Hallo</b></string>
    <string name="july_text"><b>Hallo2</b></string>
    <string name="august_text"><b>BLINDTEXT</b></string>
    <string name="september_text"><b>BLINDTEXT</b></string>
    <string name="october_text"><b>BLINDTEXT</b></string>
    <string name="november_text"><b>BLINDTEXT</b></string>
    <string name="december_text"><b>BLINDTEXT</b></string>
    <string name="january"><b>January</b></string>
    <string name="february"><b>February</b></string>
    <string name="march"><b>March</b></string>
    <string name="april"><b>April</b></string>
    <string name="may"><b>May</b></string>
    <string name="june"><b>June</b></string>
    <string name="july"><b>July</b></string>
    <string name="august"><b>August</b></string>
    <string name="september"><b>September</b></string>
    <string name="october"><b>October</b></string>
    <string name="november"><b>November</b></string>
    <string name="december"><b>December</b></string>

    <string name="flowers"><b>Flowers</b></string>
    <string name="calender">calender</string>
    <string name="plants">plants</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="bushes">Bushes</string>
    <string name="bushes_text">BLINDTEXT</string>
    <string name="fruittree">Fruit Trees</string>
    <string name="fruittree_text">BLINDTEXT</string>



</resources>
